we need to write a method called
multiply
that takes two arguments and returns the
product of the two arguments
which are going to be numbers
so let's define our method multiply
and we need to define two parameters
we'll call them
number one and number two because we
know we want to return the product of
the two numbers
we can simply multiply them within our
method
because line two is the last line
executed in our multiply method
the return value of multiplying these
two numbers together
will be the return value of the method
we can invoke the multiply method and
we'll pass in
4 and 2 as our arguments so we'll expect
that the return value of the multiply
method will be 8.
and so we can see that let's output the
return value
with put us so let's run our program
and we see 8 as we were expecting
you